save.co.uk 2010-08-19

# Privacy Policy - Save.co.uk

Last Updated: 24 February 2010

This is the Privacy Policy of Save.co.uk Inc. ("Save.co.uk" or "us" or "we"). ****

This statement is made in light of the requirements of the Data Protection Act 1998 (the "Act") in order to alert you to our data processing practices which will govern how any Personal Information we collect from you will be processed. 

Our Terms and Conditions, which incorporate by reference this Privacy Policy, govern your use of our online services, any content or information therein, the Save.co.uk website, any sub-domains of Save.co.uk, and any other website pages on which services are provided by us (collectively, the "Site").We are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. Our Privacy Policy was developed as an extension of our commitment to combine quality coupons and deals for products and services with integrity in dealing with our users. Our Privacy Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect, use and store the personal information you provide to us.

Please read the Terms and Conditions and this Privacy Policy carefully. Our Terms and Conditions and Privacy Policy may be modified by us from time to time. Any modifications we make will be effective immediately upon posting to the Site and the effective date of the latest version of the Privacy Policy will appear on this page. It is your responsibility to regularly check the Site to determine if there have been changes to the Terms and Conditions or the Privacy Policy and to review the changes.

To ask us questions or offer comments, please contact us at the email address provided below.

**What Information Do We Collect?**

When you visit the Site, you may provide us with two types of information: information you actively choose to disclose ("Active Information") and information collected in a way not visible to you on an aggregate, anonymous basis as you and others browse our Site ("Passive Information").

When we refer to "personal information" we mean information that can be linked to a specific individual, such as a name, address, telephone number, or email address. Sharing personal information with us is entirely optional.

**No Use of Our Site by Persons Under 13**

The Site is not intended for use by anyone under 18, except with the explicit permission and under the supervision of a parent or guardian who accepts full legal responsibility for the minor's use. No person under 13 should disclose information on this Site. We don't knowingly collect or use personal information from children under 13. If a child under 13 has provided us with personal information without parental or guardian consent, the parent or guardian should contact us at the email address provided below to remove the information and opt out of promotional opportunities. You may learn more about protecting children's privacy online by visiting [http://clickcleverclicksafe.direct.gov.uk](http://clickcleverclicksafe.direct.gov.uk/).

**Active Information You Choose to Provide**

You may choose to provide us with personal information, such as your email address, name, and postal address, to register with the Site and to receive coupons by email or other services or information. 

You may also choose to provide your post code on the Site to receive information about products and services in your area.

**Passive Information We Collect**

Our Site utilizes a standard technology called "cookies" to collect information about how our Site is used. Passive Information gathered may include your Internet service provider, browser type, operating system, the date and time of visits, the Site pages viewed, time spent at our Site, and the sites visited just before and just after our Site. Passive Information is collected on an aggregate basis without any association to your personal information so that you remain anonymous. If you do not wish to transmit "cookie" information about yourself, you may turn off the cookie function in your web browser; please consult the "Help" section of your browser to correctly do so. If you elect to turn off cookies, however, you may not be able to access certain features of the Site and your use of some portions of the Site may be affected.

**What is a Cookie?**

Cookies are a feature of web browser (Internet Explorer, Firefox, etc.) software that allows web servers to recognize the computer used to access a site. They are small pieces of data that are stored by a user's web browser on one site to simplify subsequent interactions with that site by the same user or to use the information to streamline the user's transaction on related web pages. This makes it easier for a user to move from site to site and to complete transactions over the Internet. Cookies should make your online experience easier and more personalized. The Interactive Advertising Bureau (Europe) has produced a series of web pages (see [http://www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/)) which explain how cookies work and how they can be managed. 

**How Do We Use the Information Collected?**

**Active Information**

We will use the Active Information you provide us to deliver the content, features, advertising, services, or information you request. If you provide your email address, we may send you information or other messages related to your activities on the Site or about our services. We may retain the Active Information you provide and a record of the service or information provided. Any Active Information retained would be used to assist the delivery of the content, features, advertising, services, or information you requested, and to optimize your experience and enhance the quality of the time you spend with us online. We may use the Active Information you provide to us to contact you about changes to our Site, new services, features or products we offer, or other information we think you will find valuable. If at any time you do not wish to receive such information, please send us an email at webmaster@save.co.uk or click on the "unsubscribe" link contained in any message that we send to you. When you send us a message, we retain the content of the message, your email address, and any information you may provide to us, including your experience with the Site, and your contact preferences, as well as the response we send back to you. This helps us manage any follow-up questions you may have, measure how effectively we address your concerns, and improve the Site.

We may share Active Information with persons we employ directly, or as contractors or agents at our direction, for purposes of administering our business activities, providing customer services such as support, and making available other product or service offers or deals we think may be of interest to you.

We may disclose your personal information to any member of our group, which means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company and its subsidiaries. 

If we or substantially all of our assets are acquired by another company, your personal information will be shared with our new owner, but it will remain subject to the terms of the then-applicable privacy policy or another set of terms if you agree to them. 

**Passive Information**

We use Passive Information to enhance and design our Site to make it easier, faster and friendlier to use, and to optimize your experience and enhance the quality of the time you spend with us online. Additionally, cookies help us know information about how many people visit our Site, when they visit and how they use our service. Passive Information is collected on an aggregate basis and we do not connect any of this information to your email address or other personal information. However, Passive Information may result in your viewing of particular content, features, advertising, services, or information based on your user habits or your viewing on our Site.

We may also allow third parties, such as advertisers on our Site, to place cookies on our Site so we can help enhance your online experience after you leave our Site. The third party cookies used on our Site are also designed to improve your online experience by facilitating the receipt of targeted advertisements while on our Site and while you are viewing other, non-Save.co.uk web sites. These third parties may use information about your visits to our and other web sites obtained through their cookie (which does NOT include your name, address, e-mail address or telephone number) in combination with non-personal information about your purchases and interests from other online sites in order to provide advertisements for goods and services of interest to you. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies and not ours.

We also may share web site usage information about visitors to our Site with third parties, such as advertisers on our Site, for the purpose of managing and targeting advertisements and for market research analysis on our Site and other sites. For these purposes, we and our third-party advertising companies may place pixel tags (also called clear gifs) on some of the pages you visit on our Site. We will then use the information that is collected using these pixel tags to serve you relevant advertisements when you are visiting other sites on the Internet. These advertisements may be targeted to specific searches you conducted on Save.co.uk ****during earlier browsing sessions.

If you would like more information about the information collection practices of third-party advertising companies and your choices about not having the information described above used by these companies or opting out of online preference marketing, please visit [www.youronlinechoices.co.uk](http://www.youronlinechoices.co.uk/).

**Your Information and Links to Other Web Sites**

This Site contains links to other websites not owned by us that may have different privacy practices from ours. We aren't responsible for the content or privacy practices of those sites, and our Privacy Policy doesn't apply to information collected by those sites. You should read those sites' privacy policies to make sure you agree to them before using such sites. If you choose to visit or shop at such sites, you should read their privacy policies to make sure you agree to them before making purchases.

**Sharing Information with Advertisers or Other Third Parties**

We may share with third parties, such as advertisers on our Site or other website operators, anonymous, aggregated information about user habits, characteristics and user patterns. We may use your IP address and share it with third parties to help diagnose problems with our servers, to manage the Site, and to enhance the Site based on usage pattern data.

**Sharing Information with the Government or As Otherwise Required by Law**

We may also use or disclose information to resolve disputes or investigate problems. We may disclose or access information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it, or if we consider it necessary to maintain service and improve our products and services.

**Protection of your Personal Information**

In an effort to prevent unauthorized access, disclosure or accidental loss or destruction of Active Information or Passive Information, we use reasonable efforts to secure the information you provide. Although we take reasonable steps to safeguard and prevent unauthorized access to your personal information, we can't be responsible for the acts of those who gain unauthorized access, and we make no warranty, express, implied or otherwise, that we will prevent such access. Communications you may have with us via email or postal mail may not be secure unless we advise you that security measures are in place prior to your sending information. Therefore, if you choose to communicate with us through these means, you are assuming the risk of doing so and we request that you do not send or post sensitive information through these means.

**International Users**

This Site is hosted and operated in the United States of America.

Those who access or use the Site from other jurisdictions do so at their own choice and risk and are solely responsible for compliance with local law. Please note that the personal information you submit to our Site will be transferred to and stored in the United States to be processed by us so we can provide this Site to you as set forth in this Privacy Policy and the Terms and Conditions. ****

It may also be processed by staff operating in the United States or other destination outside the EEA who work for one of our suppliers. Such staff maybe engaged in, among other things, the processing of your details and the provision of support services.

By submitting your personal information, you acknowledge and agree that we may collect and use your personal information and that we may transfer to or store or process your personal information in the United States. Please note that the level of legal protection provided in the United States or other non-EEA countries in which you may access our Site may not be as stringent as that under European Union privacy standards or the privacy laws of some other countries, possibly including your home jurisdiction.

**Your Rights and Contacting Save.co.uk About Your Information or Information You Receive**

We have a legal obligation to ensure that your personal information is kept accurate and up to date. Please assist us to comply with this obligation by ensuring that you inform us of any changes to your personal information. 

You have the right to request details of the information we hold about you and to delete or rectify any inaccurate information about you by sending us a written request to privacy@save.co.uk stating your full name and your address. Any access request may be subject to a fee of £10 to meet our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you.

You have the right to ask us not to process your personal information for marketing purposes. We will usually inform you (before collecting your information) if we intend to use your information for such purposes and will always inform you if we intend to disclose your information to any third party for such purposes. You can exercise your right to prevent such processing by checking certain boxes on the forms we use to collect your information. If you desire not to receive information about products or services we think may be of interest to you , wish to access, delete or correct you information or wish to exercise your right to prevent us processing your personal information for marketing purposes, please send us an email to privacy@save.co.uk. 

If you have questions or concerns about our collection, use or disclosure of your personal information, please write to us at:

Privacy  
Save.co.uk Inc.  
3 Golf Center, Suite 241  
Hoffman Estates, IL 60169  
USA
